venum.com 2019-05-24

# PRIVACY POLICY | Venum.com US

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This policy sets out the ways your personal data will be processed by us.

**The coverage of this privacy policy**

This policy covers how Venum Fight treats personal information that Venum Fight collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Venum Fight products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

**The customer information we collect**

We collect the following data (we use Magento, Google Analytics, Criteo, Facebook & Zendesk):

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site. This includes information provided at the time of opening an account, subscribing to our Newsletters, ordering products or when requesting further services or information from us.
  * Information about your computer including where available: your IP address, operating system and browser type.
  * Information about your Internet usage obtained using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. You can refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the sending of cookies.

We do not receive any of your credit card or financial details from payments handled on our behalf by the payment provider Ogone.

If you don't allow us to collect your personal information, we may not be able to deliver certain services to you, and some of them may not be able to take account of your interests and preferences. If you have questions about the specific personal information about you that we process or retain, and your rights regarding that personal information, please  **[contact us](https://euro.venum.com/en/contact/)**.

**The way we use customer information**

You can register with our website if you would like to take advantage of our newsletter and other features. You may receive updates on our news and site features. Information you submit on our website will not be used for these purposes unless you specifically fill out the newsletter form.

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.
